A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.38 (A2013) FA473
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2013.095: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1991-2012; AC_2013_095; 26.2 Cubic Feet 20 standard record storage boxes, R4105-4124; 20 standard record storage boxes, R4105-R4124
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, AC_2013_095_120; 10.48 Cubic Feet 8 record storage boxes
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Cassells, Cyrus Curtis), 2005-2006 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Chambers, Veronica Victoria), 2005-2006 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Clark, Sonya Y. S.) (CO-RESIDENT: Drewal, Henry John), 2005-2006 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Coffey, Susanna J.), 2005-2006 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Cohen, Jerome), 2005-2006 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Colistete, Renato Perim), 2006 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Cooper, Richard Stanley), 2005-2006 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Cortez, Jayne Edward), 2005-2006 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Cramton, Peter), 2006 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Crile, Susan), 2005-2006 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Cruz, Conchitina Riboroso), 2006-2007 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Cutschall, Colleen Antoinette), 2005-2006 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Datta, Bishakha), 2005-2006 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (de Oliveira, Jocy), 2005-2007 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (de Zegher, Catherine), 2006-2007 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Derricotte, Toi M.), 2005-2006 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Deveaux, Monique Louise), 2005-2007 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (DiNovelli, Donna Marie), 2005-2006 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Dresser, Mark S.) (CO-RESIDENT: Lapp, Sarah Jane), 2006-2007 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (DuPlessis, Rachel Blau), 2006-2007 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Durieux-Smith, Andr?e H.), 2005-2008 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Dwamena-Aboagye, Angela ), 2006 (Box R4107)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Edwards, Melvin E.), 2005-2006 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Encanto, Georgina Reyes), 2005-2007 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Ess, Barbara), 2006-2007 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Evans, Nicholas David), 2005-2007 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Eylon, Bat-Sheva ) (CO-RESIDENT: Linn, Marcia C.), 2006-2007 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Eysenck, Michael William), 2006-2007 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Fainstein, Norman), 2005-2007 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Fainstein, Susan S.), 2005-2007 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Feinstein, Andrew Josef), 2005-2006 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Fligstein, Neil D.), 2006-2007 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Fogelin, Robert J.), 2005-2006 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Freed, Curt R.), 2006-2007 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Galaty, John G.), 2006-2007 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Gentner, Dedre), 2005-2006 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Gilmour, Joan Marie), 2005-2006 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Goldman, Lee), 2005-2006 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Goldstein, Ann), 2005-2007 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Goldstein, Susan Jane) (CO-RESIDENT: Scheepers, Esca), 2005-2007 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Gordillo, Gaston Rafael), 2006-2007 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Gordon, Russell T.), 2005-2006 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Gorodetsky, Gabriel), 2006-2007 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Greene, Jack P.) (CO-RESIDENT: Wood, Gordon S.), 2005-2006 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Gross, Kenneth), 2006-2007 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Guardia de Alfaro, Gloria A.), 2005-2007 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Hacker, Peter Michael) (CO-RESIDENT: Schulte, Joachim), 2005-2006 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Hamilton, Kendra Yvette), 2005-2006 (Box R4108)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Hanawalt, Barbara A.), 2005-2006 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Harding, Helen Ronnie), 2004-2009 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Harrison, Brian Howard), 2005-2007 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Haunschild, Pamela R.), 2005-2006 (Box R4109)
    - 120 Resident Haunschild, Pamela R. - Steve Utt (Spose of P. Haunschild) 2006 - Still Image, 2005-2006; 2013:095:002 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Hayes, Denis A.), 2005-2006 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Hedstr?m, Peter M.E.), 2006-2007 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Herdt, Gilbert), 2005-2006 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Hess, Stephen), 2005-2007 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Hill, Constance Valis), 2006-2007 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Holm, Darryl D.), 2005-2007 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Holt, John Clifford), 2005-2009 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Howard, Mildred); (CO-RESIDENT: Myer, Mychael), 2006-2007 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Howe, Fanny Q.), 2004-2006 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Hulsebosch, Daniel), 2006-2007 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Inman, Robert P.), 2006 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Jacobs, Harvey M.), 2005-2006 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Jayaraman, Saru) (CO-RESIDENT: Mamdouh, Fekkak), 2005-2006 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Jewell, Nicholas P.), 2005-2007 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Joiner, Thomas), 2005-2006 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Jovicic, Natasa), 2004-2007 (Box R4109)
    - 2013.095.047 - RES 120 - Jasenovac Memorial Site - Published Material, 2004-2007; 2013:095:047 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Juvelis, Joy Ann), 2005-2007 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Kaiser, Susan B.) (CO-RESIDENT: Rabine, Leslie W.), 2004-2006 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Kapur, Ravinder Lal), 2005-2006 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Karthikeyan, Chandrasekaran), 2005-2006 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Kenny, Anthony John) (CO-RESIDENT: Kenny, Charles James), 2005-2006 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Kleeblatt, Norman L.), 2006-2009 (Box R4109)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Koltsova, Elena (Olessia)), 2005-2006 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Krepon, Michael), 2006-2009 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Kriegel, Uriah), 2005-2007 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Kumar, Vijaya), 2006-2007 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Lardner, George E.), 2005-2006 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Lasky, Kathryn), 2006-2007 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Levi, Jonathan A.), 2006-2007 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Macdonald, Cynthia Ann), 2004-2006 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Maestripieri, Dario), 2006 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Mahaffy, Jake), 2006-2007 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Mahajan, Sucheta), 2006-2007 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (McCoy, Barry M.), 2006-2008 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Mitchell, Donald Mark) (CO-RESIDENT: Staeheli, Lynn A.), 2005-2006 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Miyagawa, Chiori), 2005-2006 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Mortensen, Dale T.) (CO-RESIDENT: Pissarides, Christopher A.), 2006 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Muller, Arnold Michael), 2006-2007 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (No?, Luis Felipe), 2006 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Noland, Marcus), 2005-2007 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Norris, Margot), 2005-2007 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Osada, Moto), 2005-2007 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Paarlberg, Robert L.), 2005-2007 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Pearlin, Leonard I.), 2005-2006 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Peruzzotti, Enrique), 2005-2007 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Peterson, Robert Edwin), 2005-2007 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Pierce, Jennifer L.), 2005-2006 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Porzecanski, Teresa), 2004-2006 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Prudencio, Cergio), 2006-2007 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Pushpamala, Narasingarao), 2005-2006 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Qayum, Seemin) (CO-RESIDENT: Ray, Raka), 2005-2006 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Raffman, Diana), 2006 (Box R4110)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Ramaprasad, Jyotika), 2005-2007 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Ramirez-Valles, Jesus), 2005-2006 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Reed, Arden), 2005-2007 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Reiss, Carol Shoshkes), 2005-2007 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Ringrose, David Robert), 2005-2006 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Roberts, Helen May), 2005-2006 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Robison, Bruce H.), 2006 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Rocamora, Carol), 2005-2007 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Rosenberg, Norman J.), 2005-2006 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Roy, Parama), 2006-2008 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Rucker, Paul Nathaniel), 2005-2006 (Box R4111)
    - 120 Resident Rucker, Paul Nathaniel - Paul Rucker History of an Apology - Digital, 2005-2006; 2013:095:003 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Salter, Mary Jo), 2006-2007 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (San Juan, Epifanio), 2005-2006 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Sandweiss, Martha A.), 2006-2007 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Saxe, Geoffrey B.), 2005-2006 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Sethi, Rumina), 2005-2006 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Shabecoff, Alice) (CO-RESIDENT: Shabecoff, Philip), 2004-2006 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Sharma, Sushil), 2005-2008 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Sharov, Vladimir), 2006-2009 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Shemesh, Aharon), 2005-2006 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Siebert, Horst), 2005-2006 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Silver, Diana R.) (CO-RESIDENT: Weitzman, Beth C.), 2006-2007 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Smilevski, Goce), 2005-2006 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Smith, Douglas C.), 2005-2009 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Smith, Laurence C.), 2006 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Sober, Elliott R.), 2005-2006 (Box R4111)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Sogbedji, Mianikpo Jean), 2005-2007 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Solomon, Andrew Wallace), 2005-2007 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Spear, Richard E.), 2005-2007 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Stacey, Judith), 2005-2006 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Szpiro, George G.), 2005-2007 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Tacha, Athena), 2005-2007 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Tatum, James H.), 2005-2007 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Thayil, Jeet Jacob), 2005-2006 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Theofanidis, Christopher), 2005-2009 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Thomas, Jeffrey W.), 2006 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Thurston, Anne F.), 2005-2007 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Tiberius, Valerie), 2005-2006 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Urofsky, Melvin I.), 2006-2009 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Vernon-Feagans, Lynne), 2006 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Viriyachaiyo, Vilaiwan), 2005-2006 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Viscomi, Joseph S.), 2005-2006 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Waldman, Anne L.), 2005-2006 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Wartgow, Jerome F.), 2005-2006 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Wedeen, Lisa J.), 2005-2006 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Wellman, Henry M.), 2006-2007 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Welner, Kevin Grant), 2004-2006 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (West, Catherine Paige), 2005-2006 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Wiles, David Patrick), 2005-2006 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Williams, Amy C.), 2005-2006 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Wolchik, Sharon L.) (CO-RESIDENT: Bunce, Valerie Jane), 2006-2007 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Worboys, Michael), 2005-2007 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Wrigley, Robert), 2006-2007 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Yee, Sienho), 2004-2007 (Box R4112)
    - 120 - RESIDENT (Zubok, Vladislav M.), 2006-2007 (Box R4112)
  - Search (SRC), AC_2013_095_1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2008 SRC 146 - SYNERGOS INSTITUTE - COMMUNITY PARTICIPATION AND URBAN DEVELOPMENT IN SAO PAULO, BRAZIL, 2008-2009 (Box R4113)
    - 2008 SRC 147 - HESPERIAN FOUNDATION - ONLINE DIGITAL HEALTH LIBRARY, 2008-2010 (Box R4113)
    - 2008 SRC 150 - KENYA INFORMATION AND COMMUNICATION TECHNOLOGY BOARD - DEVELOPMENT OF BUSINESS PROCESS OUTSOURCING SECTOR, 2008-2009 (Box R4113)
    - 2008 SRC 152 - BROOKINGS INSTITUTION - "STATE OF THE NATION'S METRO AREAS" REPORT, 2008-2010 (Box R4113)
    - 2008 SRC 154 - NATIONAL HOUSING TRUST - TAX EXEMPT HOUSING BONDS AND TRANSIT-RICH COMMUNITIES, 2008-2009 (Box R4113)
    - 2008 SRC 155 - INSTITUTE FOR TRANSPORTATION AND DEVELOPMENT POLICY - TRANSPORTATION MODELS FOR REPLICATION IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2008-2010 (Box R4113)
    - 2008 SRC 158 - AFRICAN AGRICULTURAL TECHNOLOGY FOUNDATION - ASSESSING CHINESE AGRICULTURAL TECHNOLOGIES FOR AFRICAN FARMERS, 2008-2010 (Box R4113)
    - 2008 SRC 159 - AGA KHAN UNIVERSITY (PAKISTAN) - eHEALTH ASSOCIATION, 2008-2011 (Box R4113)
    - 2008 SRC 164 - AFRICAN CENTER FOR ECONOMIC TRANSFORMATION - ADVISORY AND RESEARCH SERVICES ON AFRICA'S ENGAGEMENT WITH CHINA, 2008-2010 (Box R4113)
    - 2008 SRC 165 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - CONFERENCE ON THE U.S. HOUSING CRISIS, 2008-2010 (Box R4113)
    - 2008 SRC 169 - NORTHEASTERN UNIVERSITY - TRANSPORTATION EQUITY POLICY RESEARCH, 2008-2011 (Box R4113)
    - 2008 SRC 171 - WATER AND SANITATION FOR THE URBAN POOR (ENGLAND) - IMPROVING SYSTEMS IN NAIROBI, KENYA, 2008-2010 (Box R4113)
    - 2008 SRC 179 - ROYAL UNIVERSITY COLLEGE OF FINE ARTS (SWEDEN) - MEETING ON URBAN FINANCING INNOVATION, 2008-2009 (Box R4113)
    - 2008 SRC 184 - BROOKINGS INSTITUTION - URBAN FINANCING LANDSCAPING IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 2008-2010 (Box R4113)
    - 2000 SRC184 - Final Report for Brookings Grant 2008 SRC 184 - Digital, 2008-2010; 2013:095:004 (Box R4113)
    - 2008 SRC 187 - KENYA RED CROSS SOCIETY - EMERGENCY OPERATIONS CENTER, 2008-2012 (Box R4113)
    - 2008 SRC 197 - BROOKINGS INSTITUTION - ADVANCE METROPOLITAN AND NATIONAL PROSPERITY, 2008-2009 (Box R4113)
  - Health Equity (HE), AC_2013_095_2; 14.41 Cubic Feet 11 record storage boxes
    - 2000 HE 005 - PAN AMERICAN HEALTH ORGANIZATION - CAPAPCITY BUILDING AND GENDER EQUITY (1 and 1 SUPPL. FOLDER), 1999-2005 (Box R4114)
    - 2000 HE 005- Proyecto Genero, Equidad, y Reforma de la Saude - Digital, 1999-2005; 2013:095:005 (Box R4114)
    - 2000 HE005 - Indicadores Basico Para el Analisis de la Equidad de Genero en Salud - Published Material, 1999-2005; 2013:095:007 (Box R4114)
    - 2000 HE 005 - Procesos de reforma des sector salud y programas - Published Material, 1999-2005; 2013:095:008 (Box R4114)
    - 2000 HE 005 - Reforma del Sector Salud y Derechos Sexuales y Reproductivos - Published Material, 1999-2005; 2013:095:009 (Box R4114)
    - 2000 HE 039 - IPAS - ADOLESCENT SEXUAL AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH IN AFRICA, 2000-2001 (Box R4114)
    - 2001 HE 055 - MEXICAN HEALTH FOUNDATION - HEALTH RESEARCH AWARD, 2000-2004 (Box R4114)
    - 2001 HE 055 - Reformas del Sector Salud y Salud Sexual y Reproductiva - Published Material, 2000-2004; 2013:095:006 (Box R4114)
    - 2001 HE 074 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - FIRST INTERACADEMY MEDICAL PANEL CONFERENCE, 2001-2005 (Box R4114)
    - 2001 HE 074 - Inter Academy Medical Panel (IAMP) Confronting Infections, Antibiotic - Published Material, 2001-2005; 2013:095:010 (Box R4114)
    - UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE MALAYSIA - CLEARINGHOUSE ON TOBACCO CONTROL (1 and 2 SUPPL.), 2000-2006 (Box R4114, Box R4115)
    - 2001 HE 075 - Annual Progress Report 2002 - Digital, 2000-2006; 2013:095:011 (Box R4115)
    - 2001 HE 075 - UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE MALAYSIA - CLEARINGHOUSE ON TOBACCO CONTROL (1and 2 SUPPL.), 2000-2006 (Box R4115)
    - 2001 HE 075 - CTOB Info Kit: A Compilation of Multimedia Presentations - 11 Digital, 2000-2006; 2013:095:012-2013:095:022 (Box R4115)
    - 2001 HE075 - List of Educational CD ROM-Based Toolkits - 11 Digital, 2000-2006; 2013:095:023-2013:095:033 (Box R4115)
    - 2001 HE 075 - Malaysian Council for Tobacco Control: Progressive Report 2004 - Digital, 2000-2006; 2013:095:034 (Box R4115)
    - 2001 HE 093 - KUNMING MEDICAL COLLEGE (CHINA) - SEXUALITY ISSUES IN THE MEKONG REGION, 2001-2004 (Box R4115)
    - 2001 HE093 - Cross-Border Sexuality in the Greater Mekong Sub-Region - Published Material, 2001-2004; 2013:095:035 (Box R4115)
    - 2001 HE 097 - WOMEN'S DIGNITY PROJECT - GENDER AND HEALTH EQUITY LENS ON OBSTETRIC FISTULA IN EAST AFRICA, 2001-2006 (Box R4115)
    - 2001 HE 102 - (HEALTH EQUITY) - TOBACCO AND LIVELIHOODS IN ASIA, 2001-2005 (Box R4115)
    - 2000 HE 042 - INCLEN TRUST INTERNATIONAL (PHILIPPINES) - GENERAL SUPPORT (2 FOLDERS), 2000-2006 (Box R4116)
    - 2000 HE 043 - (HEALTH EQUITY) - GLOBAL TB DRUG FACILITY, 2000-2004 (Box R4116)
    - 2000 HE 048 - THOMAS JEFFERSON UNIVERSITY - GLOBAL NETWORK FOR PERINATAL AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH (2 FOLDERS), 2000-2005 (Box R4116)
    - 2001 HE 006 - International Union Against Cancer (Switzerland) - Distance-Learning on Tobacco Control, 2000-2006 (Box R4117)
    - 2001 HE 011 - POPULATION COUNCIL - ADOLESCENT SEXUAL AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH IN GHANA, 2001-2006 (Box R4117)
    - 2001 HE 013 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - MILLENNIUM HEALTH RESEARCH AWARDS, 1999-2005 (Box R4117)
    - 2001 HE 023 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - EQUITY GAUGE INITIATIVE, 2001-2007 (Box R4117)
    - 2001 HE023 - Urban Health Inequities - Digital, 2001-2007; 2013:095:036 (Box R4117)
    - 2001 HE 107 - UNIVERSITY OF CAPE TOWN (SOUTH AFRICA) - ALPS (AFFORDABILITY LADDER PROGRAM) PROJECT, 2001-2008 (Box R4117)
    - 2001 HE 107 - Training Materials Promoting Equitable Access to Health Care for Households - Digital, 2001-2008; 2013:095:037 (Box R4117)
    - 2001 HE 108 - MARGA INSTITUTE (SRI LANKA) - ALPS (AFFORDABILITY LADDER PROGRAM) PROJECT, 2001-2004 (Box R4117)
    - 2001 HE 108 - (unlabeled) - 2 Digital, 2001-2004; 2013:095:038, 2013:095:039 (Box R4117)
    - 2001 HE 109 - INDIAN INSTITUTE OF MANAGEMENT BANGALORE - ALPS (AFFORDABILITY LADDER PROGRAM) PROJECT, 2001-2007 (Box R4117)
    - 2001 HE 110 - VIETNAM - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - ALPS (AFFORDABILITY LADDER PROGRAM) PROJECT, 2001-2005 (Box R4117)
    - 2001 HE 112 - NATIONAL PUBLIC HEALTH INSTITUTE (FINLAND) - BC CONFERENCE: LEADERS OF PRIMARY NATIONAL PUBLIC HEALTH INSTITUTIONS, 2001-2005 (Box R4117)
    - 2001 HE 113 - LONDON SCHOOL OF HYGIENE AND TROPICAL MEDICINE, UNIVERSITY OF LONDON (ENGLAND) - TOBACCO INDUSTRY IN SOUTHEAST ASIA, 2001-2005 (Box R4117)
    - 2001 HE 116 - POPULATION COUNCIL - IMPACT OF QUALITY OF CARE ON WOMEN'S REPRODUCTIVE BEHAVIOR (2 FOLDERS), 1994-2004 (Box R4118)
    - 2001 HE 128 - IPAS - REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH IN ETHIOPIA, KENYA, TANZANIA AND ZIMBABWE, 2001-2006 (Box R4118)
    - 2001 HE 130 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - PUBLIC HEALTH SCHOOLS WITHOUT WALLS (4 FOLDERS), 1992-2006 (Box R4118, Box R4119)
    - 2002 HE 001 - WOMEN'S MEDIA CENTRE OF CAMBODIA - TOBACCO CONTROL CAMPAIGN, 2001-2005 (Box R4119)
    - 2002 HE 008 - UNIVERSITY OF OTTAWA (CANADA) - GLOBAL HEALTH EQUITY GAUGE, 2000-2004 (Box R4119)
    - 2002 HE 009 - UNITED NATIONS HUMAN SETTLEMENTS PROGRAMME (KENYA) - HIV/AIDS AND ORPHANS SHELTER PROGRAM, 2001-2004 (Box R4119)
    - 2002 HE 015 - GRANTMAKERS IN HEALTH - HEALTH RELATED ACTIVITIES, 1999-2005 (Box R4119)
    - 2002 HE 025 - MCGILL UNIVERSITY (CANADA) - COST/BENEFITS OF DOTS FOR TB IN DOMINICAN REPUBLIC, HAITI AND MEXICO, 2002-2005 (Box R4119)
    - 2002 HE 027 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - INTEGRATE EQUITY INTO HEALTH PROGRAMS IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 2002-2005 (Box R4120)
    - 2002 HE 030 - CONSULTATION OF INVESTMENT IN HEALTH PROMOTION (VIETNAM) - GENDER, SEXUALITY AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH, 2002-2005 (Box R4120)
    - 2002 HE 033 - ALLIANCE FOR MICROBICIDE DEVELOPMENT - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2002-2006 (Box R4120)
    - 2002 HE 036 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - HIV INTERVENTIONS IN TANZANIA, 2002-2004 (Box R4120)
    - 2002 HE 043 - HANOI SCHOOL OF PUBLIC HEALTH (VIETNAM) - PUBLIC HEALTH (1 and 1 SUPPL.), 1991-2005 (Box R4120)
    - 2002 HE 047 - IBNSINA (PAKISTAN) - PUBLIC HEALTH TRAINING IN AFGHANISTAN, 2002-2005 (Box R4120)
    - 2002 HE 048 - GHANA - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - ADOLESCENT SEXUAL AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH (2 FOLDERS), 2001-2011 (Box R4120)
    - 2002 HE 053 - PROGRAM FOR APPROPRIATE TECHNOLOGY IN HEALTH - BC CONFERENCE: NEW AND UNDERUTILIZED TECHNOLOGIES TO REDUCE MATERNAL MORTALITY, 2002-2004 (Box R4121)
    - 2002 HE 053 - Seks Aman Dan Media di Asia Tenggara: Meniti Paradoks: Indonesia - Published Material, 2002-2004; 2013:095:040 (Box R4121)
    - 2002 HE 053 - Tihn Duc Toan Va Cong Tac Truyen Thong o Dong Nam A: Vietnam - Published Material, 2002-2004; 2013:095:041 (Box R4121)
    - 2002 HE 053 - International Journal for Gynecology and Obstetrics - Published Material, 2002-2004; 2013:095:042 (Box R4121)
    - 2002 HE 055 - NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF LAOS - PARENT-CHILD INTERACTION ON SEXUAL ATTITUDES AND BEHAVIOURS OF YOUTH, 1998-2005 (Box R4121)
    - 2002 HE 057 - AIDS SOCIETY OF THE PHILIPPINES - CONGRESS ON AIDS AND SYMPOSIUM ON SEXUALITY AND MEDIA (1 and 1 SUPPL. FOLDER), 2001-2006 (Box R4121)
    - 2002 HE 057 - Media and Sexuality: Between Sensationalism and Censorship - Published Material, 2001-2006; 2013:095:043 (Box R4121)
    - 2002 HE 057 - Safe Sex and the Media in Southeast Asia: Fettered Thoughts, Uncovered Sex - Digital, 2001-2006; 2013:095:044 (Box R4121)
    - 2002 HE 057 - Safe Sex and the Media in Southeast Asia - Published Material, 2001-2006; 2013:095:045 (Box R4121)
    - 2002 HE 060 - KENYA MEDICAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - USE OF AMOXICILLIN IN THE TREATMENT OF BRONCHITIS IN HIV-INFECTED ADULTS, 2001-2005 (Box R4121)
    - 2002 HE 062 - INTERNATIONAL PLANNED PARENTHOOD FEDERATION (ENGLAND) - LEADERSHIP TRANSITION PROCESS, 2002-2006 (Box R4121)
    - 2002 HE 063 - ARIZONA STATE UNIVERSITY - MEETING ON PLANT-BASED VACCINES FOR HUMANS AND ANIMALS, 2002-2006 (Box R4121)
    - 2002 HE 064 - AGA KHAN UNIVERSITY (PAKISTAN) - WORKSHOPS ON HEALTH CARE AND BENCHMARKS OF FAIRNESS, 2002-2005 (Box R4121)
    - 2002 HE 067 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - GLOBAL ANTI-TB DRUG RESISTANCE SURVEILLANCE PROJECT, 2002-2005 (Box R4121)
    - 2002 HE 068 - AMERICAN SOCIAL HISTORY PRODUCTIONS - TV SERIES ON ECOLOGY OF INFECTIOUS DISEASE, 2002-2005 (Box R4122)
    - 2002 HE 069 - PAN AMERICAN HEALTH ORGANIZATION - DENGUE WORKSHOP, 2002-2005 (Box R4122)
    - 2002 HE 075 - MAHIDOL UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - ASIA PACIFIC CONFERENCE ON REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH AND SEXUALITY, 2002-2004 (Box R4122)
    - 2002 HE 077 - TUFTS UNIVERSITY - CHILD HEALTH EQUITY, 2002-2005 (Box R4122)
    - 2002 HE 080 - INTERNATIONAL DEVELOPMENT ENTERPRISES - VIETNAMESE TOBACCO CONTROL PROGRAM, 2002-2006 (Box R4122)
    - 2002 HE 081 - CHINA - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - HEALTH SECTOR REFORM AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH AND GENDER ISSUES, 2002-2005 (Box R4122)
    - 2002 HE 082 - (HEALTH EQUITY) - INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS IN HEALTH (2 FOLDERS), 2001-2004 (Box R4122)
    - 2002 HE 083 - UNIVERISTIY OF ILLINOIS - ECONOMICS OF TOBACCO USE AND CONTROL IN SOUTHEAST ASIA (CHICAGO), 2000-2006 (Box R4122)
    - 2002 HE 086 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - GLOBAL TOBACCO CONTROL IN SOUTHEAST ASIA, 2000-2005 (Box R4123)
    - 2002 HE 087 - UNIVERSITY OF THE PHILIPPINES, DILIMAN - RESEARCH AWARDS PROGRAM ON GENTER, SEXUALITY AND SEXUAL HEALTH, 2002-2005 (Box R4123)
    - 2002 HE 090 - BIOMEDICAL RESEARCH AND TRAINING INSTITUTE (ZIMBABWE) - TB INFECTION IN NURSES AND CHRONIC COUGH AMONG PATIENTS, 2002-2006 (Box R4123)
    - 2002 HE 091 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR RESEARCH ON WOMEN - PUBLICATIONS ON MICROBICIDES, 2001-2002 (Box R4123)
    - 2002 HE 098 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA - DENGUE CONTROL PILOT PROJECT IN NICARAGUA (BERKELEY), 2002-2004 (Box R4123)
    - 2002 HE 100 - ESSENTIAL INFORMATION - CORE SUPPORT AND COMPULSORY LICENSING PROJECT, 2002-2005 (Box R4123)
    - 2002 HE 101 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR RESEARCH ON WOMEN - ADOLESCENT SEXUALITY AND FERTILITY IN MAHARASHTRA, INDIA (3 FOLDERS), 1992-2008 (Box R4123, Box R4124)
    - 2002 HE 101 - Community-Based Health Care: Lessons from Bangladesh to Boston - Published Material, 1992-2008; 2013:095:046 (Box R4124)